Guide to the Cornell University Library Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections exhibition materials, 1992-2018
Cornell University Library Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections exhibition materials, 1992-2018.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Library Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections exhibition materials, 1992-2018
13-6-3306
Cornell University. Library. Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections.
10 cubic ft.
Pamphlets, posters, note cards
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Division exhibit items, records, and related material.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Division was formed in 1992 with the combination of the Department of Rare Books, the Department of Manuscripts and University Archives, the History of Science Collections, and the Icelandic Collection.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Division exhibit items, records, and related material.
Also DVDs of Reunion and other exhibition-related lectures including "History of Wine," by Thomas Pinney, June 5, 2008; "The Collector and the Editor: Tales from the Mark Twain Papers," Robert H. Hirst, April 23, 2010; and "All Full of Tears and Flapdoodle: The Genius of Mark Twain," June 10, 2010.
Copy of exhibition guest book and visitor questionnaires, 2008-2009.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. Library. Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections.; Cornell University--Libraries.
Subjects:
Library exhibits.; Libraries--New York (State)--Special collections.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. General Library Files
Series II. Exhibits: Undated, 1951-1990
Series III. Exhibits: 1991-2000
Series IV. Exhibits: 2001-2016
CONTAINER LIST
- General Library Files
  - Exhibition Mounts (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Hirshland Gallery lighting (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Museum loans (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Exhibition loan forms (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Conservation forms (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Kroch stationary (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Stevens Icelandic documents (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Nancy Dean notes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Exhibit schedule, 1994-2005 (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
  - General, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Ideas for future exhibits (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Exhibition publicity (Box 1, Folder 13-14)
  - Exhibit Funds, Parker and Tofias (Box 1, Folder 15-16)
  - NEH Funding pamphlets (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Exhibit workshop, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Exhibit case designs (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Exhibit guest books, 2004-2014 (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
  - Broadside lists for exhibits (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Exhibit ideas, Nancy Dean (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - General exhibit cards, unknown exhibitions (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Exhibits: Undated, 1951-1990
  - Medieval Botany, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - For the Heart and Mind: American Gift Books and Literary Annuals of the Nineteenth Century, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Drafts for early exhibit cards, Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Hilda Sachs labels, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Shapiro Dedications (Hebraica), Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Archives exhibit, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Clarke Family case maps and labels, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Student Activities: 4 Seasons of the Year labels, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Haskins Society, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Elizabeth Reed Dedication, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Hoy Field Baseball, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - French Revolution, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - French Revolution labels, Undated (Box 9, Folder 1-4)
  - Emancipation Proclamation, Undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Samuel Johnson, Undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Cornell Alumni of Color labels, Undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Literary Autograph labels, Undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Nobel prize winners, Undated (Box 9, Folder 6-8)
  - 1977 reunion displays and exhibit information, Undated (Folder 1)
  - A Cornell Author: Vladimir Nobokov labels, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - History of Science materials (large envelopes of cards) (Box 10)
    Cooper Collection, 1990; Will that building stay up?, 1990; Andrew D. White and the History of Science, 1965 & 1982; Christmas Rose, 1983-4; parrots, 1984; Lavoisier (Grolier exhibit cards); Adelmann; acquisitions, new, 1974; acquisitions, recent, 1975; "An Affair of the Heart," 1983; bindings, 1981; "The Blue Jay and Its Illustrators," 1983; calculating instruments & books containing calculating devices, 1980; "coaching and carriage design," 1974; Elliot - Monograph of the Pittidae, 1983; facsimiles of famous works, 1976, 400th anniversary of Wm. Harvey's birth, 1978; "Health of Scholars," 1982; horse books, 1974; Robert Jameson, 1974; Marcello Malpighi's 350th birthday anniversary, 1978; oil resources, 1974; Joseph Prestele, 1982; "Reckoning with Figures"; Dorothy Schullian, 1989; "A Season for Remembering," 1980, 1982 envelopes)
  - History of Science materials (letter size envelopes of cards) (Box 10)
    Academia del Cimento, 1966; Aranzio and embryology, 1964; Laura Bassi, Physicist, 1966; Claude Bernard, 1978; the Bunsen burner, 1964; "Monuments in Clinical Medicine," 1964; Sir Humphry Davy, 1965; "Early Accounts of the Moon," 1965; Fabricius, teacher of Harvey, 1963; famous dissertations in embryology and anatomy, 1963; Goethe and color, 1966; Harvey, Dr. William, 1963; recent acquisitions in the history of geology, 1964; history of science collections, 1964; first editions of Johann Kepler, 1964; Lavoisier; books from Lavoisier's library; Leeuwenhoek and the microscope; Mendel's experiments, 1965; "Multum In Parvo," 1962; "Not recorded in NUC," 1963; printing of science and the mind of man, 1963; books in the History of Science, 1966; Ready Reckoners, 1964; Rösel von Rosenhof's insects, 1965; Mauro Rusconi, 1965; Seba's cabinet of natural history, 1964; Niels Stensen, 1964; Emanuel Swedenborg, 1964; Trilussa's dental caricatures, 1965; Andreas Vesalius, Anatomist, 1964; William Whewell, 1966
  - History of Science exhibition materials (small envelopes of cards) (Box 10)
    Jacques Gautier D'Agoty, 1970; anthropology exhibit, 1976; Petrus Apianus, 1967; apples, 1966; Audubon, John James; The Bent and Broken Moon, 1969; Thomas Bewick, 1978; bindings by Ivan Ruzicka, 1973; bleaching and dyeing, 1968; Boncompagni's birthday, 1978; the Boyle collection, 1981; watercolors from Brunfels' herbal, 1977; A Salute to George Lincoln Burr, 1972; Cannabis sativa, 1970; Christmas Rose and Star of Bethlehem, 1975; the Clepsydra, 1969; Curtis' Botanical Magazine, 1982; Henry Pelouze de Forest, Cornellian 1971; early mining, 1967; Charles Estienne as anatomist, 1967; fabulous animals, 1969; facsimile editions, 1968; five Jesuit scientists, 1968; the Jay Gould cable, 1966; Albrecht von Haller, 1977; the Hollister collection, 1967; Ithaca imprints, 1968; "It's Raining Violets," 1971; "Je Le Pansay; Diew Le Guarit," 1967; treasures of Mann Library, 1977; Meleagris gallopavo, 1968; medical dissertations, 1970; music in science, 1968; natural history museums, 1972; Ornithogallum umbellatum; 1969; Eliot Porter, the seasons, 1970; the quetzal, 1971; Rédouté: liliacées, 1970; roses in June, 1970 & 1982; scientific incunabula, 1969; scientific medals, 1969 (?); "Self-Poised upon that Yellow Flower," 1967; silkworms, 1969; suspension bridges, 1970; tea, 1969; tides, 1968; travel books of science, 1968; imitators of Vesalius, 1967; Vesuvius, 1969; Viscum album, 1969-1970; Andrew D. White and the History of Science, 1965; wine making, 1971; exhibit for College of Agriculture alumni, 1977; exhibit for Will Provine's History of Science classes, 1974; exhibit for S.L.A. Upstate N.Y. meeting, 1974; L. P. Williams History of Science class; 1976; recent acquisitions: December 1972; January-September, November-December 1973; March-June, September-October, December 1974; February-December 1975; January-December 1976; January-November 1977; January, June-October 1978
  - History of Science exhibition materials: box of small miscellaneous cards (Box 10)
  - Autograph exhibit labels, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Clothing: A Reflection of Cultural Changes, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Clothing: A Reflection of Cultural Change poster, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Shaw at Cornell: The Burgunder Collection, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Reunion, ca. 1975 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Tompkins County exhibit cards, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Political Americana exhibition materials, 1976-1988 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Lavoisier files, 1979, 1983-1984, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Department reading room exhibition case, 1980s (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Political Campaign Collections, Nancy Dean's folder, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Ephemera exhibit, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Javanese Postcards file, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Cornell Library exhibition, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 42-44)
  - Alumni exhibit in Barton Hall, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Nancy Dean exhibit ideas, 1982-1991 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Reunion notes, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Presidential exhibit, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Presidential Campaign, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Political Americana, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Shaw files and labels, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - 40th Anniversary, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Urban America: Documenting the Planners, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 6-15)
    Catalog documents and photos, notes, mailing lists, labels, case maps, and publicity
  - Urban America: Documenting the Planners posters, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 25th Anniversary of Olin Library, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Women's History, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Reunion, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Railroad exhibit, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Presidential Elections, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 20-21)
  - Ithaca Centennial Exhibit, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 22-26)
    Publicity, notes, labels, and case maps
  - Ezra Cornell / Early Years, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Case maps, publicity, and labels
  - Cornell 1889, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Cornell Theatre in honor of the opening of the Performing Arts Center, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - A Celebration of Theatre, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Chimes and the Library, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Cornell Charter, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Cornell and China, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - 125th Anniversary of the University, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 34-35)
    Also in NYC
  - 125th Anniversary of the University, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - 125th Anniversary of the University poster, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Various posters from library-related events (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Reunion, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Exhibits: 1991-2000
  - Home Economics, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Home Economics poster, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Valentine Exhibition, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Student Activities, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Reunion, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Letter Writers and Books of Etiquette, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Educating Women, Spring 1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Psychology, Summer 1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 100th Anniversary of Uris Library, Fall 1991 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Anna Botsford Comstock, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1936 Women Children's Literature Fund, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Children's Literature: From England to America, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 14-15)
    Publicity, labels, and notes
  - Children's Literature: From England to America poster, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 14-15)
  - Cornell Chimes, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Hungarian Political Posters Exhibition, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Presidential Exhibit, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Fine Printers Finely Bound Too, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
    Includes catalog
  - Fine Printers Finely Bound Too poster, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Preserving the Past, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Literary Sites: Scenes from Nabokov's Life and Works, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Literary Sites: Scenes from Nabokov's Life and Works poster, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - "Wish you Were Here!": An Exhibition of Early Postcards from the Rare and Manuscript Collections, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Cornell-Penn Football, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - In Her Own Hand: An Exhibition of Women's Diaries, Letters, and Memoirs, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - In Her Own Hand: An Exhibition of Women's Diaries, Letters, and Memoirs poster, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - SA McCarthy dedication of reading room in Olin, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - The Chemistry of Revolution: The Life and Death of Lavoisier, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - The Chemistry of Revolution: The Life and Death of Lavoisier poster, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - A Revolution in Color: Chiaroscuro Woodcuts from the Permanent Collection (Johnson Museum), 1994 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Courtship, Love, and the Pursuit of Passion in Old Master Prints (Johnson Museum), 1994 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Nature by Design, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Paper, Leather, Clay and Stone: The Written Word Materialized, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 10-11)
  - Ruptures in the Landscapes: Revisiting Romantic England, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Ruptures in the Landscapes: Revisiting Romantic England poster, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Possible exhibition of Cornell memorabilia, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Women's Suffrage items for Johnson Museum exhibit, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - 40th Anniversary of the Library, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 34-35)
  - Remembering Cornell, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 36-39)
    Labels, case maps, notes, pamphlets, and publicity
  - Remembering Cornell president biographies, mounted on red plastic, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Hans Albrecht Bethe: 60 Years at Cornell, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 1-4)
    Notes, correspondence, case labels, and publicity
  - Hans Albrecht Bethe: 60 Years at Cornell poster, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 1-4)
  - A Legacy of Ideas, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 125 Years of Achievement: The History of Cornell's College of Architecture, Art, and Planning, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 125 Years of Achievement: The History of Cornell's College of Architecture, Art, and Planning labels, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Invention and Enterprise: Ezra Cornell, a Nineteenth-Century Life, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Artistry of Elfriede Abbe, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Johnson Museum exhibit pamphlets, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Nobel Prize in Physics posters, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - I Take This Pen In Hand: Letters Home from Everyday People, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - The Well-Tempered Collection: Music Resources at Cornell University, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - "The Instinct of and Artist": Shaw and the Theatre, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 12-43)
    Labels, catalog, publicity, notes, negatives and reproductions, and correspondence
  - Laura (Riding) Jackson and the Promise of Language, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 44-50)
    Notes, item lists, pamphlets, brochures, labels, and publicity
  - Ammonsfest, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Reunion, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Medieval Studies at Cornell, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - The Art of the Book, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - Nabokov Centenary Festival Exhibition, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 3-7)
  - Women Challenging Gender, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Johnson Museum exhibit loans, pamphlets, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Johnson Museum exhibit loans, correspondence, pamphlets, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Chimes display, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Pramoedya, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Pramoedya poster, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Beautiful Birds: Masterpieces from the Hill Ornithology Collection, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Beautiful Birds: Masterpieces from the Hill Ornithology Collection posters, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Alison Lurie: Writer at Work, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Alison Lurie: Writer at Work poster, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - William Wordsworth and the Romantic Imagination, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - William Wordsworth and the Romantic Imagination posters and event posters, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Library exhibit, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Living and Reliving the Icelandic Sagas, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Photographs of the exhibit, publicity, catalog, notes
  - Living and Reliving the Icelandic Sagas posters, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Nature's Garland: Illustrated Botanical Works from Cornell University Library, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Nature's Garland: Illustrated Botanical Works from Cornell University Library posters, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Phrenology, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Vote! An Exhibition of Political Americana, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Human Ecology small exhibition, ca. 2000 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Cornell's East Asia Program, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Exhibits: 2001-2016
  - Shaw Festival booklet, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - From Domesticity to Modernity: What Was Home Economics?, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - From Domesticity to Modernity: What Was Home Economics? posters and signed poster, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Treasures of the Asia Collections, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Treasures of the Asia Collections posters, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Not by Bread Alone: America's Culinary Heritage, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Not by Bread Alone: America's Culinary Heritage posters, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Political Americana, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Asia Exhibition notes, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Women in the Literary Marketplace: 1800-1900, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 29-30)
  - Women in the Literary Marketplace: 1800-1900 posters, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Olin 101 Winter exhibit, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Frankenstein, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Gravely Gorgeous: Gargoyles, 19th century imagination, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Dragon Day, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Women in Veterinary Medicine, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 7 Millionth Volume, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Gettysburg Address, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Reunion poster, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Artifex: Leonard Baskin and Gehenna Press, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 14-15)
  - Artifex: Leonard Baskin and Gehenna Press posters, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - The Evolution of the Medieval Book, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - The Evolution of the Medieval Book posters, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Mozart and the Keyboard Culture of His Time, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Mozart and the Keyboard Culture of His Time posters, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Black History Month Exhibit, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 18-19)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha display labels, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - "I Will Be Heard": Abolitionism in America, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 21-29)
    Guest book, VHS, Images, labels, notes
  - "I Will Be Heard": Abolitionism in America posters, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 21-29)
  - Barbara Eden request, exhibit in Olin, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Get Out the Vote!, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Get Out the Vote! posters, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - George Jean Nathan reference room case, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Legacy of Leadership, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Liberty Hyde Bailey: A Man for All Seasons, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 34-35)
  - Liberty Hyde Bailey: A Man for All Seasons Poster, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Tianjin, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Pastimes and Paradigms: Games We Play, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Pastimes and Paradigms: Games We Play posters, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Cornellians in the Olympics, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - 12 Black Classicists, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Vanished Worlds, Enduring People: Cornell University Library's Native American Collection, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 40-42)
    Notes, labels, publicity, and photographs of reception
  - Vanished Worlds, Enduring People: Cornell University Library's Native American Collection posters, 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Lolita 50th Anniversary, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - AAFCS, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Early Black Women at Cornell, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - The Passionate Collector: Willard Fiske and His Libraries, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - The Passionate Collector: Willard Fiske and His Libraries poster, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - James Joyce: From Dublin to Ithaca, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 5-7)
  - James Joyce: From Dublin to Ithaca poster, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Winter Activities, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Gatsby Exhibition, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Edgar Allan Poe, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 9-15)
    Catalog, drafts, publicity, labels, and notes
  - Edgar Allan Poe poster, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 1956 Reunion, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Darwin Day, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Highlights of Historic Religions, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Baldwin Memorial Stairway, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - In the Founders' Footsteps, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - In the Founders' Footsteps posters, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - HRC, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - HRC poster, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - "I Would Found and Institution": the Ezra Cornell Bicentennial, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - "I Would Found and Institution": the Ezra Cornell Bicentennial poster, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Happy Birthday Ezra banner, 2007 (Box 11)
  - LaFayette: Citizen of Two Worlds, 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 23-28)
    Publicity, drafts, notes, and labels.
  - LaFayette: Citizen of Two Worlds poster, 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 23-28)
  - Southeast Asian Buddhist Manuscripts, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - AAFCS, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Wason 40th Anniversary, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 27-28)
  - Rose Goldsen Archive of New Media Art event poster, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Song of the Vine: A History of Wine, 2008-2009 (Box 7, Folder 31-33)
  - Song of the Vine: A History of Wine poster, 2008-2009 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - NCAA Exhibition, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Charles Darwin: After the Origin, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 2-3)
  - Darwin Day poster, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Strunk and White's Elements of Style, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Lincoln Presidency: Last Full Measure of Devotion, 2009-2010 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - The Lincoln Presidency: Last Full Measure of Devotion, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - The Lincoln Presidency: Last Full Measure of Devotion poster, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - The Art and Life of Alison Mason Kingsbury, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1960 Anniversary, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Known to Everyone, Liked by All: The Business of Being Mark Twain, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Known to Everyone, Liked by All: The Business of Being Mark Twain poster, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Android Dreams, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Laura Riding Jackson in the 21st Century, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Werner-Pfeiffer: Book-objects and Artist Books, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Werner-Pfeiffer: Book-objects and Artist Books poster, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Asia Reunion labels, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 9-12)
  - Animal Legends: From the Trojan Horse to Godzilla, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Animal Legends: From the Trojan Horse to Godzilla posters, 2011 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Commencement 1911, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Dawn’s Early Light: The First 50 Years of American Photography, 2011-2012 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Dawn’s Early Light: The First 50 Years of American Photography posters, 2011-2012 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Cornellians on the Titanic, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 15-16)
  - Cornellians in the Olympics, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - The Cornell Papyrus, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Remembering Lincoln at Gettysburg, 2013 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Speaking of Sex posters, 2014 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 150 Ways to Say Cornell, 2014-2015 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - 150 Ways to Say Cornell posters, 2014-2015 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Gods and Scholars, 2015-2016 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Signal to Code, 2016 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Punkfest Cornell: Anarchy in the Archives, 2016 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Martin Dominguez Exhibit at Museo ICO, Madrid Spain, 2017-2018 (Box 8, Folder 30)